<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Draft on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</title><link>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/status/draft/</link><description>Recent content in Draft on Newton Evolution Proposals (NEPs)</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://nepdemo.newton.bio/status/draft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NEAT Backed Currency (NBC)</title><link>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-23/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-23/</guid><description>Simple Summary # NEAT Backed Currency (NBC) is a kind of cryptographically secured currency following the design protocol of NEAT. The goal of this creation is the allow anyone to create a set of exchangeable, and divisible asset that can be securely exchanged using the platform provided by Newton Community. We used the term community, because the distributed security, must be backed by a community of infrastructure providers and a rather healthy exchange community.</description></item><item><title>NewChain MainNet Opening</title><link>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-27/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-27/</guid><description>Simple Summary # After NewChain TestNet successful opening, NewChain MainNet is going to be opened by inviting the community to setup, run and maintain the ledger nodes.
Abstract # In current stage, NewChain MainNet would still run with PoA (Proof-of-Authority) consensus mechanism for producing blocks. Hence a certain amount of staking would be required for keeping the ledger nodes honest and not be malicious to harm the network.</description></item><item><title>NewPay Community Node Migration</title><link>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-29/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-29/</guid><description>Simple Summary # As part of the NewChain MainNet opening strategy and upgrading plan, the current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay for virtual mining would be migrated and resolved for paving the way of NewChain to embrace a more bright future.
This proposal will illustrate a possible solution for migrating them to be integrated into the NewSwap mining framework to also benefit the development of NewSwap.
Abstract # The current &amp;ldquo;community nodes&amp;rdquo; in NewPay are doing &amp;ldquo;virtual mining&amp;rdquo; nowadays for daily released NEW from NewPool.</description></item><item><title>Newton Encoded Asset Transaction (NEAT)</title><link>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-20/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-20/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Newton Encoded Asset Transaction(NEAT) defines the root data type for all asset exchanges. Once a new record of NEAT is registered into Newchain, it represents a form of irrefutable accountability based on the immutable features of Newchain. To help transaction assess the worthiness of transactions before their commitment, all transactions have a common field, called: Bounded Accountability, which defines all known exit conditions when a transactional process is breached.</description></item><item><title>Newton Pre-paid Card (NPC)</title><link>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-24/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nepdemo.newton.bio/neps/nep-24/</guid><description>Simple Summary # Newton Pre-paid Card (NPC) is a cryptographically insured asset that works with exchangeable assets within the Newton Community. It can be extended to issue Membership Card, Score Cards, or even Balanced Score Cards. It can also possess negotiating powers in attaining tangible goods. For example, one may pre-pay for editable goods, such as vegetable, milk, or beef, or other kinds of commercially viable goods. The basic assumptions about NPC is that it provides a classification scheme to define goods.</description></item></channel></rss>